Seung-Woo Nam

PhD Candidate

Personal Profile

I am a PhD candidate at OEQELAB, Seoul National University. I was formerly supervised by the late Prof. Byoungho Lee and currently supervised by Prof. Yoonchan Jeong. Prior to this, I received my BS degree in Electrical and Computer Engineering from Seoul National University. My research area includes holography, AR/VR, computational displays, visual perception, and metasurfaces.

Education

09/2019 - Present	Ph.D. Electrical and Computer Engineering, Seoul National University, Korea. Advisor: Byoungho Lee, Yoonchan Jeong
03/2015 - 08/2019	B.S. Electrical and Computer Engineering, Seoul National University, Korea.
03/2012 - 02/2015	Gyeonggi Science High School for the Gifted, Korea.

Work Experience

09/2024 - 10/2024	Visiting Student Researcher, Stanford University, CA, USA
	- Stanford Computational Imaging Lab led by Prof. Gordon Wetzstein
06/2023 - 12/2023	Research Scientist Intern, Meta Reality Labs, WA, USA

Publications

First Author (* Denotes equal contribution)

- [7] S. Lee*, **S.-W. Nam***, K. Rio, R. Landig, H.-H. Cheng, L. Lu, and B. Silverstein, "Perceptual Evaluation of Steered Retinal Projection," ACM *SIGGRAPH 2024* Conference Proceedings
- [6] D. Kim*, **S.-W. Nam***, S. Choi*, J.-M. Seo, G. Wetzstein, and Y. Jeong, "Holographic Parallax Improves 3D Perceptual Realism," ACM Transactions on Graphics *(SIGGRAPH 2024)*
- [5] S.-W. Nam*, Y. Kim*, D. Kim, and Y. Jeong, "Depolarized Holography with Polarization-multiplexing Metasurface," ACM Transactions on Graphics (SIGGRAPH ASIA 2023)
- [4] D. Kim*, S.-W. Nam*, B. Lee, J.-M. Seo, and B. Lee, "Accommodative holography: improving accommodation response for perceptually realistic holographic displays," ACM Transactions on Graphics (SIG-GRAPH 2022)
- [3] **S.-W. Nam**, D. Kim, and B, Lee, "Accelerating a spatially varying aberration correction of holographic displays with low-rank approximation," Optics Letters, 2022 *(Editor's pick)*
- [2] D. Kim*, **S.-W. Nam***, K. Bang, B. Lee, S. Lee, Y. Jeong, J.-M. Seo, and B. Lee, "Vision-correcting holographic display: evaluation of aberration correcting hologram," Biomedical Optics Express, 2021
- [1] **S.-W. Nam**, S. Moon, B. Lee, D. Kim, S. Lee, C.-K. Lee, and B. Lee, "Aberration-corrected full-color holographic augmented reality near-eye display using a Pancharatnam-Berry phase lens," Optics Express, 2020.

Co-Author

[10] E. Lee, Y. Jo, **S.-W. Nam**, M. Chae, C. Chun, Y. Kim, Y. Jeong, and B. Lee, "Speckle reduced holographic display system with a jointly optimized rotating phase mask," Optics Letters, 2024

- [9] C. Chen, **S-W. Nam**, D. Kim, J. Lee, Y. Jeong, and B. Lee, "Ultrahigh-fidelity full-color holographic display via color-aware optimization," PhotoniX, 2024
- [8] S. Lee, **S.-W. Nam**, J. Lee, Y. Jeong, and B, Lee, "HoloSR: deep learning-based super-resolution for real-time high-resolution computer-generated holograms," Optics Express, 2024.
- [7] D. Lee, K. Bang, **S.-W. Nam**, B. Lee, D. Kim, and B. Lee, "Expanding energy envelope in holographic display via mutually coherent multi-directional illumination," Scientific Reports, 2022.
- [6] D. Yoo, **S.-W. Nam**, Y. Jo, S. Moon, C.-K. Lee, and B. Lee, "Learning-based compensation of spatially varying aberrations for holographic display [Invited]," Journal of the Optical Society of America A, 2022.
- [5] D. Yoo, Y. Jo, **S.-W. Nam**, C. Chen, and B. Lee, "Optimization of computer-generated holograms featuring phase randomness control," Optics Letters, 2021.
- [4] S. Lee*, D. Kim*, **S.-W. Nam**, B. Lee, J. Cho, and B. Lee, "Light source optimization for partially coherent holographic displays with consideration of speckle contrast, resolution, and depth of field," Scientific Reports, 2020.
- [3] S. Lee, D. Kim, **S.-W. Nam**, and B. Lee, "Speckle reduced holographic displays usi.ng tomographic synthesis," Optics Letters, 2020
- [2] S. Moon, **S.-W. Nam**, Y. Jeong, C.-K. Lee, H.-S. Lee, and B. Lee, "Compact augmented reality combiner using Pancharatnam-Berry phase lens," IEEE Photonics Technology Letters, 2020.
- [1] S. Moon, C.-K. Lee, **S.-W. Nam**, C. Jang, G.-Y. Lee, W. Seo, G. Sung, H.-S. Lee, and B. Lee, "Augmented reality near-eye display using Pancharatnam-Berry phase lenses," Scientific Reports, 2019.

Research Demos

08/2024 Holographic Parallax, SIGGRAPH 2024 Emerging Technologies

08/2022 Lenslet VR, IMID 2022 Exhibition

Honors and Awards

2020 – 2024	Korea Foundation for Advanced Studies (KFAS) Graduate Study Scholarship
2023	Silver prize, Samsung Display Industry-University Cooperation Paper Award 2023
2020	Best Poster Paper Awards, The 20th International Meeting on Information Display
2015 – 2018	National Science and Engineering Undergraduate Scholarship

Services

Reviewer ACM Transactions on Graphics, IEEE ISMAR, Optics Letters, Applied Optics, ETRI Journal

Reference

Prof. Yoonchan Jeong Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering, Seoul National University

Tel) +82-02-880-1788 Email) yoonchan@snu.ac.kr

Prof. Gordon Wetzstein Department of Electrical Engineering, Stanford University

Tel) +1-650-497-7953 Email) gordon.wetzstein@stanford.edu